YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 9. Photographs
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. PRINTS AND NEGATIVES
  - Subseries B. National Board and National Administrative Office
    - Buildings and Properties
      - Geneva Conference Grounds, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin (Box 988, Folder 14)
      - Grace Dodge Hotel, Washington, D.C. (Box 988, Folder 15)
      - Leadership Development Center, Phoenix, Arizona (Box 988, Folder 16)
      - National Headquarters
        - Early sites (Box 989, Folder 1)
        - 600 Lexington Ave./135 East 52nd St., New York City (1912-82)
          - General (Box 989, Folder 2)
          - Postcards (Box 989, Folder 3)
          - Photo album, circa 1912 (Box 989, Folder 4)
          - Photo series by Bevil Knapp and Richard Freund, 1981: contact sheets and negatives (Box 989, Folder 5)
          - Photo series taken for booklet "Photo Memories of '600': Contact sheets and negatives, circa 1982, [see following files for larger prints] (Box 989, Folder 6-9)
          - Move and demolition (Box 989, Folder 10)
          - Exteriors
            - Lexington Ave. side (Box 989, Folder 11)
            - 52nd St. side (Box 989, Folder 12)
            - Roof and Views (Box 990, Folder 1)
          - Interiors
            - General (Box 990, Folder 2)
            - Archives and Library (Box 990, Folder 3)
            - Assembly Room, second floor (Box 990, Folder 4)
            - Doorways (Box 990, Folder 5)
            - First floor (Box 990, Folder 6)
            - Fixtures (Box 990, Folder 7)
            - Furniture (Box 990, Folder 8)
            - Halls, Stairways, and Elevator (Box 990, Folder 9)
            - Light Fixtures (Box 990, Folder 10)
            - Offices (Box 990, Folder 11)
            - Reception Room, first floor (Box 990, Folder 12)
            - Training School/Residence
              - General (Box 990, Folder 13)
              - Solarium (Box 990, Folder 14)
            - Twelfth Floor (Box 990, Folder 15)
        - 726 Broadway (1984-97)
          - Contact Sheets (Box 991, Folder 1)
          - Negatives (Box 991, Folder 2)
        - Silver Bay Conference Grounds, Lake George, NY (Box 991, Folder 3)
    - Finance and Development
      - General, 1965, 1980s (Box 992, Folder 1)
      - Committee: World Service Council, circa 1916-93 (Box 992, Folder 2-7)
      - Fundraising
        - Tribute to Women in [International] Industry (TWIN)
          - Award statue (Box 992, Folder 8)
          - 1978 (New York City)
            - Contact sheets (Box 992, Folder 9)
            - Awards Dinner and United Nations Reception (Box 992, Folder 10)
            - Committees (Box 992, Folder 11)
            - Honorees (Box 992, Folder 12)
            - Press Reception (Box 992, Folder 13)
            - Seminar and Luncheon (Box 992, Folder 14)
          - 1981 (San Francisco)
            - Contact sheets and negatives (Box 992, Folder 15)
            - General (Box 992, Folder 16)
            - Committees (Box 992, Folder 17)
            - Honorees (Box 992, Folder 18)
          - 1983 (Houston)
            - Contact sheets and negatives (Box 993, Folder 1-2)
            - General (Box 993, Folder 3)
          - 1986 (Boston)
            - Contact sheets and negatives (Box 993, Folder 4)
            - General (Box 993, Folder 5)
          - 1987 (Kansas City)
            - Contact sheets and negatives (Box 993, Folder 6)
            - Seminar (Box 993, Folder 7)
      - Fundraising Campaigns
        - Round the World Reconstruction Fund, 1947 (Box 993, Folder 8)
        - Fund for the Future
          - Miscellaneous events (Box 993, Folder 9)
          - Luncheon, 1982 (Box 993, Folder 10)
          - Washington DC Reception, 16 Feb 1984 (Box 993, Folder 11)
          - Strategy meeting, 12 Sep 1984 (Box 993, Folder 12)
          - National YWCA Headquarters Reception, Nov 1984 (Box 993, Folder 13)
          - Reception, 17 Apr 1985 (Box 993, Folder 14)
          - Appreciation Reception, 6 Feb 1986 (Box 993, Folder 15)
        - Millennium 2000, Genesis Group, 1994-98 (Box 993, Folder 16)
    - Publicity
      - National YWCA Week (Box 994)
        - TV Spot, 1975 (Box 994, Folder 1)
        - Goodyear Blimp, 1981 (Box 994, Folder 2)
      - White House and YWCA, 1926-93, n.d. (Box 994, Folder 3)
      - YWCA Merchandise, 1992, n.d. (Box 994, Folder 4)
      - Historical Illustrations used in YWCA Publications
        - Miscellaneous and stock (Box 994, Folder 5)
        - From article in The Century, Jun 1889 (Box 994, Folder 6)
        - By Dore Gettsten and Aurelie Astea (Box 994, Folder 7)
        - "The Story of the YWCA," 1992
          - Miscellaneous photos (Box 994, Folder 8)
          - Collages (Box 994, Folder 9)
      - Posters
        - General and miscellaneous, 1925-52, n.d. (Box 994, Folder 10)
        - Annual Campaigns, 1951-64 (Box 994, Folder 11)
        - Girl Reserve/Y-Teen, 1919-62 (Box 994, Folder 12)
        - Health and exercise, 1920, 1932, n.d. (Box 994, Folder 13)
        - Paul Bissell (artist), 1925-29 (Box 994, Folder 14)
        - World War I, 1918-20 (Box 994, Folder 15)
      - Publicity photo series
        - Miscellaneous, 1956-94, n.d. (Box 995, Folder 1)
        - Classes, 1960s
          - Miscellaneous (Box 995, Folder 2)
          - Arts and crafts (Box 995, Folder 3)
          - Personal development (Box 995, Folder 4)
        - College student by Carroll Aument, 1960 (Box 995, Folder 5)
        - "On your own but not alone," 1952 (Box 995, Folder 6)
        - Poster girls, 1959 (Box 995, Folder 7)
        - "Look Ahead," 1960 (Box 995, Folder 8)
        - "Wherever She Is" by Carroll Aument, 1959-60
          - General (Box 995, Folder 9)
          - Contact sheets and negatives (Box 995, Folder 10)
          - Y-Teen "Barbara J." (Box 995, Folder 11)
          - College student "Jean C."
            - General (Box 995, Folder 12)
            - Studying (Box 995, Folder 13)
            - Volunteering (Box 995, Folder 14)
          - Immigrant and Industrial Club member "Sophie R." (Box 995, Folder 15)
          - Resident "Peggy W." (Box 995, Folder 16)
          - Young Adult "Grace M." (Box 996, Folder 1)
          - Young Mother "Virginia B." (Box 996, Folder 2)
          - Foreign Trainee "Annama T." [Rachel Mathew] (Box 996, Folder 3)
          - Volunteer "Mrs. Charles F." [Mrs. Christy] (Box 996, Folder 4)
        - "Where You Can Belong," 1962 (Box 996, Folder 5)
        - "In Step With the 60s," circa 1963 (Box 996, Folder 6)
        - "The YWCA Belongs to You," 1964
          - General (Box 996, Folder 7)
          - Mary Jean Adams (Box 996, Folder 8)
        - "Y-Teens on the Go," 1965 (Box 996, Folder 9)
        - Poster girls, 1966 (Box 996, Folder 10)
        - "Where You Count!," circa 1969 (Box 996, Folder 11)
  - Subseries C. Conferences and Conventions
    - Conferences
      - Miscellaneous, 1903-80, n.d. (Box 997, Folder 1)
      - American Committee, Sixth Pacific Coast Conference, 1903 National (Box 997, Folder 2)
      - Institute for a Christian Basis for World Relations (aka "Vassar Institute"), Jun 1924 (Box 997, Folder 3)
      - National Women's Conference, Houston, TX, 1977 (Box 997, Folder 4)
      - United Nations World Youth Assembly, 1970 (Box 997, Folder 5)
      - Women's History Institute, Sarah Lawrence College, Jul 1979 (Box 997, Folder 6)
      - YWCA National Consultation for Programs on Domestic Violence: Battered Women, Dec 1980 (Box 997, Folder 7)
      - YWCA, [see also Subseries D. International Work; Subseries E. Program, Constituent Groups; Subseries F. Student Work]
        - City, Regional
          - Central (Lake Geneva), 1910-14, n.d. (Box 997, Folder 8)
          - Eastern (Silver Bay), 1914-16 (Box 997, Folder 9)
          - Pacific (Asilomar), 1916-29, n.d. (Box 997, Folder 10)
          - Rocky Mountain, 1920 (Box 997, Folder 11)
          - Southern (Blue Ridge)
            - Album, Jun 1912 (Box 997, Folder 12)
            - General, 1915-57, n.d. (Box 997, Folder 13)
        - County/Town and County, 1912-25 (Box 997, Folder 14)
    - Conventions
      - 4th, (Richmond)-23rd, (Cleveland)1913, 1964 (Box 998, Folder 1-8)
      - 25th, 1970 (Houston)
        - General (Box 999, Folder 1)
        - Snapshots (Box 999, Folder 2)
        - Teens and Students (Box 999, Folder 3)
        - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 999, Folder 4)
      - 26th, 1973 (San Diego)
        - Discussion Groups (Box 999, Folder 5)
        - Ethnic Participants (Box 999, Folder 6)
        - Exhibits (Box 999, Folder 7)
        - "Faces of Convention" (Box 999, Folder 8)
        - Informal Groups (Box 999, Folder 9)
        - Plenary Sessions (Box 999, Folder 10)
        - Wounded Knee Demonstration (Box 999, Folder 11)
        - Youth Constituencies (Box 999, Folder 12)
      - 27th, 1976 (South Bend, Indiana-Notre Dame)
        - Informal Groups (Box 999, Folder 13)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 999, Folder 14)
        - Plenary Sessions (Box 999, Folder 15)
        - Portraits (Box 999, Folder 16)
      - 28th, 1979 (Dallas) (Box 999, Folder 17)
      - 29th, (Washington, D.C.) 1982
        - Preparation: National Nominating Committee meetings, 1981-82 (Box 1000, Folder 1)
        - General (Box 1000, Folder 2)
        - Exhibits (Box 1000, Folder 3)
        - Contact Sheets (Box 1000, Folder 4)
        - Negatives (Box 1000, Folder 5-7)
      - 1988 31st, (Chicago) (Box 1000, Folder 8)
      - 32nd, (Atlanta) 1991
        - General (Box 1000, Folder 9)
        - World Service Council Dinner at the Carter Center (Box 1000, Folder 10)
        - Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 1000, Folder 11)
      - 33rd, 1994 (Los Angeles) (Box 1000, Folder 12)
      - 34th, 1996 (St. Louis) (Box 1000, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D. International Work
    - Department/Division
      - General and miscellaneous, 1966-87, n.d. (Box 1001, Folder 1)
      - Asian Study Seminar, 1977 (Box 1001, Folder 2)
      - International Consultation: "Women-A Power for Change," 1974
        - Groups (Box 1001, Folder 3-4)
        - Participant portraits and snapshots (Box 1001, Folder 5)
      - International Leadership Training Project, 1954-57, n.d. (Box 1001, Folder 6)
      - International Study Conference on World Reconstruction, 1948 (Box 1001, Folder 7)
      - International Training Institute
        - General, 1959-69, n.d. (Box 1001, Folder 8)
        - Models for Movement, summer 1969 (Box 1001, Folder 9)
      - Latin America/U.S.A. Project, 1961 (Box 1001, Folder 10)
      - World Fellowship
        - General
          - Prints, 1956-76, n.d. (Box 1001, Folder 11)
          - Negatives (Box 1001, Folder 12)
        - Vesper Service/Observance at Washington National Cathedral
          - 1950-71 (Box 1001, Folder 13-15)
          - 1977, n.d. (Box 1002, Folder 1-2)
    - Countries
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 1002, Folder 3)
      - Africa: Miscellaneous (unlabelled by country), circa 1950s-81 (Box 1002, Folder 4)
      - Argentina
        - General, 1910-79 (Box 1002, Folder 5)
        - Buenos Aires Scrapbook, 1929 (Box 1002, Folder 6)
      - Australia, 1942, 1949, n.d. (Box 1002, Folder 7)
      - Bangladesh, 1981, 1983 (Box 1002, Folder 8)
      - Barbados, 1981 (Box 1002, Folder 9)
      - Belgium, c. 1910s-60s (Box 1002, Folder 10)
      - Bolivia, 1943-68 (Box 1002, Folder 11)
      - Botswana, 1969-70 (Box 1002, Folder 12)
      - Brazil
        - Buildings, 1947-62 (Box 1002, Folder 13)
        - Classes, 1958-71 (Box 1002, Folder 14)
        - Conferences, 1962-82 (Box 1003, Folder 1)
        - Local Groups and Scenes, 1943-76, n.d. (Box 1003, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1962-74, n.d. (Box 1003, Folder 3)
        - Program Activities, 1932, 1954-70 (Box 1003, Folder 4)
        - Negatives (Box 1003, Folder 5)
      - Bulgaria, n.d. (Box 1003, Folder 6)
      - Burma, 1950, n.d. (Box 1003, Folder 7)
      - Cameroon, 1964 (Box 1003, Folder 8)
      - Caribbean, 1967, 1972 (Box 1003, Folder 9)
      - Ceylon, [see Sri Lanka]
      - Chile
        - Buildings, 1956-90 (Box 1003, Folder 10)
        - Camping, 1929-67, n.d. (Box 1003, Folder 11)
        - Children, 1959-79, n.d. (Box 1004, Folder 1)
        - Health, 1960s, n.d. (Box 1004, Folder 2)
        - Mothers' Club, 1960-67 (Box 1004, Folder 3)
        - Peace Corps Chile Project, 1962-63
          - General (Box 1004, Folder 4)
          - Mounted photo series (Box 1004, Folder 5)
        - Physical Education and Recreation, 1947, 1957, n.d. (Box 1004, Folder 6)
        - Program, 1947-67 (Box 1004, Folder 7)
        - Staff and Volunteers, 1960, 1982, n.d. (Box 1004, Folder 8)
        - Y-Teens, 1950-64 (Box 1004, Folder 9)
      - China, [see also albums in Record Group 1]
        - Buildings, 1913-44 (Box 1004, Folder 10)
        - Celebrations, Ceremonies, and Pageants, 1919-26, n.d. (Box 1004, Folder 11)
        - Children, 1922-29, 1963, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 1)
        - Classes, Literacy, 1924, 1963-71, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 2)
        - Conferences, 1908-47 (Box 1005, Folder 3)
        - Dramatics: 1922-33?, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 4)
        - Education and Recreation, 1920s-40, 1963, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 5)
        - Health and Nutrition, 1930s?, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 6)
        - Hostels, 1940s? (Box 1005, Folder 7)
        - Industrial, 1907, 1931, 1941, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous, 1915, 1921, 1985-86, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 9)
        - Negatives, n.d. (Box 1005, Folder 10)
        - Physical Education, 1915-32 (Box 1005, Folder 11)
        - Refugees and Family Sufferers, 1928, 1939, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 1)
        - Rural Work, circa 1940s, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 2)
        - Scenes, circa 1940s, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 3)
        - Snapshots from Ella Bennett, 1934-40 (Box 1006, Folder 4)
        - Staff and Volunteer Groups, 1919-40, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 5)
        - Women at Work, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 6)
      - Colombia
        - Prints, 1965-71 (Box 1006, Folder 7)
        - Negatives, 1965-71 (Box 1006, Folder 8)
      - Cuba, 1928, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 9)
      - Czech Republic and Slovakia, 1919-50?, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 10)
      - Denmark, 1981? (Box 1006, Folder 11)
      - Egypt
        - Prints, circa 1940s-67, n.d. (Box 1006, Folder 12)
        - Negatives (Box 1006, Folder 13)
      - England, 1963, [see also: Subseries E. Program, War Work: WWI] (Box 1006, Folder 14)
      - Estonia, circa 1920s (Box 1006, Folder 15)
      - Ethiopia
        - General, 1959-71 (Box 1007, Folder 1)
        - Negatives (Box 1007, Folder 2-3)
        - "The Opening of the Asmara YWCA," 1967 (Box 1007, Folder 4)
        - Vocational Training, Woman's Vocational School: 1964-71 (Box 1007, Folder 5)
      - Fiji, 1969-72, n.d. (Box 1007, Folder 6)
      - Finland, 1950s (Box 1007, Folder 7)
      - France, circa 1918, 1946-70, [see also Subseries E. Program, War Work: WWI] (Box 1007, Folder 8)
      - Germany
        - General, 1945-50s (Box 1007, Folder 9)
        - Children Rebuilding, 1945-1950s, 1960s? (Box 1007, Folder 10)
        - Negatives (Box 1007, Folder 11-12)
        - Neighborhood House, Berlin: scrapbook, 1961-62 (Box 1008, Folder 1)
        - Teens and Children, 1945-1950s (Box 1008, Folder 2)
      - Ghana, 1961-83 (Box 1008, Folder 3)
      - Greece, circa 1920-73, [See also: Turkey, Smyrna Scrapbook] (Box 1008, Folder 4)
      - Guyana, 1973 (Box 1008, Folder 5)
      - Holland, [see Netherlands]
      - Hong Kong, 1938, 1963-71 (Box 1008, Folder 6)
      - Hungary, circa 1920s (Box 1008, Folder 7)
      - India
        - Buildings, 1865-1963 (Box 1008, Folder 8)
        - Children, circa 1920s, circa 1960s-70 (Box 1008, Folder 9)
        - Classes, 1910, circa 1960s, 1969, n.d. (Box 1009, Folder 1)
        - Customs and Religious Practices, circa 1960s, 1967, n.d. (Box 1009, Folder 2)
        - Education and Recreation, 1902-26, circa 1960s, 1973 (Box 1009, Folder 3)
        - Girls Town, Madras, circa 1960s, 1963 (Box 1009, Folder 4)
        - Groups and Conferences, 1911-59, n.d. (Box 1009, Folder 5)
        - Health, 1914, 1962-63 (Box 1009, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous, 1931, n.d. (Box 1009, Folder 7)
        - Negatives (Box 1009, Folder 8-10)
        - Nutrition Project, Bombay, 1963 (Box 1009, Folder 11)
        - Women At Work, 1923, 1962, 1973, n.d. (Box 1009, Folder 12)
        - Women's Technical Training Institute, 1973-74 (Box 1010, Folder 1)
        - YWCA School of Social Work, circa 1960s, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 2)
      - Israel
        - Buildings, 1966-71, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 3)
        - Jerusalem, circa 1920s, 1940, 1960s-71, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 4)
      - Italy
        - General, circa. 1910s, 1940s (Box 1010, Folder 5)
        - Teen and Youth Classes, 1940s-67 (Box 1010, Folder 6)
        - Negatives (Box 1010, Folder 7)
      - Jamaica, 1961-67 (Box 1010, Folder 8)
      - Japan
        - Buildings, 1918-51, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 9)
        - Camping, 1949-63, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 10)
        - Celebrations, Ceremonies, and Pageants, 1918-63 (Box 1010, Folder 11)
        - Children, 1921, 1951, 1963, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 12)
        - Classes
          - Domestic Science, 1922, 1963?, 1971, n.d. (Box 1010, Folder 13)
          - English, 1930, 1963 (Box 1010, Folder 14)
          - Vocational, 1927, 1951, circa 1960s, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 1)
        - Conferences, 1907, 1920 (Box 1011, Folder 2)
        - Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1960s, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 3)
        - Flower Arrangement, Tea Ceremony, 1932, circa 1960s, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 4)
        - Groups, 1922-23, 1951, 1966, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 5)
        - Kure Scrapbook, 1948 (Box 1011, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous, 1909, 1911, 1960s, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 7)
        - Physical Education and Recreation, 1923-65, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 8)
        - Program, 1922, 1951-70 (Box 1011, Folder 9)
        - Staff and Volunteers, 1923-24, 1949-71, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 10)
        - Women at Work, circa 1920 (Box 1011, Folder 11)
        - Y-Teens
          - General, 1951-66, n.d. (Box 1011, Folder 12)
          - 1964 (Motoko Hayashi) (Box 1011, Folder 13)
          - 1964 (Taeko Matsutani) (Box 1011, Folder 14)
      - Jordan
        - General, 1960s-80s (Box 1012, Folder 1)
        - Aqabat Jaber Refugee Camp, Jericho (Box 1012)
          - Prints, 1961-72 (Box 1012, Folder 2)
          - Negatives (Box 1012, Folder 3)
        - Baqáa, Kalandia, Madaba, etc. Refugee Camps, 1968-69, 1983, n.d. (Box 1012, Folder 4)
        - Classes, 1962-64 (Box 1012, Folder 5)
        - Creche Figures, 1963-64, n.d. (Box 1012, Folder 6)
      - Kenya
        - Agriculture through Staff, 1962-71 (Box 1012, Folder 7)
        - Vocational Training through Y-teens, 1966-77 (Box 1012, Folder 8)
        - Negatives (Box 1012, Folder 9)
      - Korea
        - Buildings, 1950s-72, n.d. (Box 1012, Folder 10)
        - Children and Teens, 1954-72 (Box 1012, Folder 11)
        - Classes, 1950s-70, n.d. (Box 1013, Folder 1)
        - Dedication Service, 1970 (Box 1013, Folder 2)
        - Health, 1960-69, n.d. (Box 1013, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous, 1934, 1968-73, n.d. (Box 1013, Folder 4)
        - Negatives (Box 1013, Folder 5-8)
        - Orphans and Refugees, 1960s, 1965, n.d. (Box 1013, Folder 9)
        - Program, 1953-73, n.d. (Box 1013, Folder 10)
        - Rural Work, circa 1960-68, n.d. (Box 1013, Folder 11)
        - Staff, 1960s-72, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 1)
        - Women at Work, 1954-68, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 2)
        - Women's Enlightenment Movement, 1960? (Box 1014, Folder 3)
      - Lapland, c. 1920?, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 4)
      - Latvia and Estonia, 1923-37, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 5)
      - Lebanon
        - Buildings, 1961-68, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 6)
        - Camping, 1960-63, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 7)
        - Children, c. 1910s?, 1947-67, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 8)
        - Conference, 1960 (Box 1014, Folder 9-10)
        - Crafts, 1965, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 11)
        - Domestic Science, circa 1960s (Box 1014, Folder 12)
        - Health
          - Prints, 1968, n.d. (Box 1014, Folder 13)
          - Negatives (Box 1014, Folder 14)
        - Miscellaneous and Refugees, circa. 1910s-1920s, 1967-68, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 1)
        - Teens, 1959-68, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 2)
        - Vocational Training
          - Prints, 1910s?, 1959-69, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 3)
          - Negatives (Box 1015, Folder 4)
      - Liberia
        - Prints, 1949-70, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 5)
        - Negatives (Box 1015, Folder 6)
      - Madagascar, 1970?, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 7)
      - Malaya, 1960-68, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 8)
      - Mexico
        - Buildings, 1935-83, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 9)
        - Camping, 1950, 1954, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 10)
        - Classes, 1950s-60s?, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 11)
        - Conferences and Groups, 1949-79, n.d. (Box 1015, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous, 1920s, 1963, 1960s (Box 1015, Folder 13)
        - Negatives
          - 1 of 3 (Box 1015, Folder 14)
          - 2-3 of 3 (Box 1016, Folder 1-2)
        - Program, circa 1950s, 1960s (Box 1016, Folder 3)
        - Recreation, circa 1950s, 1960s (Box 1016, Folder 4)
      - Nepal, 1969 (Box 1016, Folder 5)
      - Netherlands, 1940s (Box 1016, Folder 6)
      - New Zealand, 1913 (Box 1016, Folder 7)
      - Nigeria, 1954-66, n.d. (Box 1016, Folder 8)
      - Pakistan, 1959-69 (Box 1016, Folder 9)
      - Panama Canal, 1932, n.d. (Box 1016, Folder 10)
      - Papua New Guinea, 1967, 1972 (Box 1016, Folder 11)
      - Peru, 1910s?, 1962-69 (Box 1016, Folder 12)
      - Philippines
        - Buildings, 1927-71 (Box 1016, Folder 13)
        - Camps, Conferences, and Groups, 1924-72, n.d. (Box 1016, Folder 14)
        - Health and Nutrition, 1948-68 (Box 1016, Folder 15)
        - Negatives (Box 1017, Folder 1-3)
        - Physical Education, 1935-63, n.d. (Box 1017, Folder 4)
        - Program, 1933-89 (Box 1017, Folder 5)
        - Recreation and Dance, circa 1942-73 (Box 1017, Folder 6)
        - Teens, 1936-66 (Box 1017, Folder 7)
        - Women at Work, 1918-74, n.d. (Box 1017, Folder 8)
      - Poland, circa 1918-23, n.d. (Box 1017, Folder 9)
      - Puerto Rico, [see Subseries G. Community Associations]
      - Rhodesia, [see Zimbabwe]
      - Roumania, circa 1920-22 (Box 1017, Folder 10)
      - Russia
        - General, circa 1910s, n.d. (Box 1017, Folder 11)
        - Photo Reports from Archangel and Vladivostok, 1919, n.d. (Box 1017, Folder 12)
      - Sierra Leone
        - 1954-67 (Box 1017, Folder 13)
        - 1968-70 (Box 1018, Folder 1)
      - Singapore, 1970 (Box 1018, Folder 2)
      - Slovakia, [see Czech Republic]
      - Somalia, 1982 (Box 1018, Folder 3)
      - South Africa
        - Buildings, 1964, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 4)
        - Children, 1966-69 (Box 1018, Folder 5)
        - Classes, 1967, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 6)
        - Conferences and Groups, 1957-87, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 7)
        - Consultation in New York, Sep 1987 (Box 1018, Folder 8)
        - Program, 1959-69, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 9)
      - South America, Miscellaneous unlabelled, 1890-1967, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 10)
      - Sri Lanka, 1963-76, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 11)
      - St. Vincent, West Indies, 1972 (Box 1018, Folder 12)
      - Surinam, 1972, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 13)
      - Sweden, 1964 (Box 1018, Folder 14)
      - Syria, circa 1910s, 1932, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 15)
      - Taiwan
        - Buildings, 1955-73, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 16)
        - Camping, 1950s-60s? (Box 1018, Folder 17)
        - Children, 1966, 1968, n.d. (Box 1018, Folder 18)
        - Classes, 1958-68 (Box 1019, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous, 1940s?-72, n.d. (Box 1019, Folder 2)
      - Tanzania, 1960s (Box 1019, Folder 3)
      - Thailand